[opening theme music playing]
FELINE FALL
- [bells clinking]
- We offer our humble prayers
to the revered
and awe-inspiring brachiosaurus deity.
We herbivores live
with the threat of death every day.
- [drip]
- Endurify us from all calamities
and cleanse us so that
we may find peace in this life.
Hey, why don't we buy a good luck charm?
Bah! But the talismans are cheaper.
Well, you don't want to
skimp on the offering.
- Come on, it's not like they work.
- [sighs] That's just rude.
- [bells clinking]
- We humbly pray
for protection and prosperity.
Come around, everyone.
Gather 'round. Purify yourselves and pray
that you may avoid being devoured.
[Melon] These types of herbivores
who come to this festival...
fools who casually enjoy
being prey in the food chain.
Hmm. But that girl, she is different.
That's why I don't understand it.
I've lived every day thinking
it might be the last day that I'm alive.
[Melon] Well, if that's true,
why bother with trying to get a degree,
if you think you're going to die anyway?
[laughs] Come on.
It's not as bleak
as you're making it sound.
It's like, even if I think I might die,
there are still some things
I hope I might achieve.
I still have goals and dreams.
[Melon] I do wonder.
Could I taste those thoughts and emotions?
Are they in her blood and flesh?
[Legoshi] Professor Lumrong.
Hmm?
How about... Melon?
I owe you for my ear.
And definitely
when you got me in the stomach,
Is this a ghost?
[chuckles]
You're actually still alive?
Feel like getting killed again?
Sorry to disappoint,
but tonight's not great for me.
Let's try another day, shall we?
- She's not gonna show up.
- Huh?
- Haru, I mean.
- Haru?
You know her?
Tonight, you're going down,
no matter what!
Oh, really?
[loud stomping]
[Haru sighs] Come on.
This is blatant kidnapping. [strains]
[grunts]
[strains] Ah!
Still waiting for an explanation!
- [grunts]
- [stomping]
- [stomps]
- Stop it. And quit stomping.
[groans] Are you gonna tell me anything?
I should be at the festival.
Yes, I hear you.
However...
Don't tell me
you're worried about that whole
letting him eat me thing I mentioned.
I told you to mind your own business.
When I meet him
I can just say it was a joke.
You can't joke with a guy like him!
Listen here. The guy you made that
offer to isn't a harmless schoolteacher.
He runs the black market
and he's tried to kill Legoshi
not once, but twice!
[gasps]
- [thunder breaks]
- [gasps]
[Melon groans, panting]
[Louis] Please, just stay here today.
[groans] Well, give me some food.
[sighs] What do you want?
Veggie sticks.
All right, then. I'll get some.
Don't do anything crazy.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[gasps] Just stop it!
What's your species, Professor?
[Melon] Huh?
Not to worry.
As you can see, I'm a gazelle.
Uh, well, the way you were
holding me wasn't romantic.
It was almost like how a carnivore catches
an herbivore right before they, uh...
Now I see.
So you must be the girl's boyfriend, huh?
[sighs] Guess I won't be
getting my birthday present then, huh?
Why'd you pick Haru?
[scoffing] Why indeed?
[laughs] It should be obvious.
- Same reason as you.
- Huh?
- Because she looks so tasty.
- [gasps]
- [Melon laughs]
- [grunts]
Oh, I'm sure you know.
They taste like nothing but sand.
What does?
- Oh. Those who die soaked in fear.
- [sighs]
[Melon laughs]
It literally changes their taste.
Prey tends to fear death
from the very day they're born.
[Legoshi] Everyone's afraid of dying.
- [Melon] Are you sure?
- [inhales sharply]
Remarkably, that little girl of yours...
she's not afraid of dying... or living.
That's why her flesh intrigues me.
[chuckles] You know,
I've grown quite fond of it.
[Melon laughs]
Just like you, I guess.
[Legoshi] No!
You don't... It's not like that.
[Melon] Ohh.
Been having a hard time
with those inner urges?
Want some medicine?
- [gun clicks]
- [Legoshi gasps, pants]
[grunts]
- [gunshots]
- [panting]
- [gunshot]
- [exclaims]
Today is my birthday, you know.
So in a way, don't you owe me?
Killing me won't do that.
It won't get you any closer to her.
[Melon] Well, here's the thing.
I pretty much do whatever I want.
I will say...
failure and I have met a few times.
I just didn't try hard enough
not to be born.
Huh? "Not to be born"?
[gasps]
[gunshots]
[Melon] My parents were reckless.
They fed their flesh
with an interspecies romance,
and as a result, something unnatural
was brought into this world.
"Unnatural"?
[Melon] Me, the mistake.
If they'd had any sense,
they wouldn't have brought
a mixed creature into this society.
Don't you agree?
[Legoshi] You're wrong.
Parents deserve our respect, our love.
- And they didn't--
- They didn't think
about anyone but themselves.
To bring a hybrid child into this world
is just a death sentence.
- Huh? It's not a death sentence.
- A painful existence.
Something the parents need to feel.
Which is why it falls on me
to exact revenge
for all the mixed children
that haven't been born yet,
before their parents give in
to their selfishness.
[inhales sharply]
Because after they're born, it's too late.
Huh. [gasps]
All of those devourings were you!
[Melon laughs] Was it?
- Or maybe it was you.
- What?
Carnivores eat herbivores,
and that's just life.
But this was an experiment.
What links interspecies relationships?
Raw, natural hunger?
Or was it indeed love?
So it was you.
You were the one behind it all.
- [gun cocks]
- [Melon laughs]
Their blood covered expressions
were frozen in bliss.
Damn you. [growls]
You're a monster.
Watch your mouth.
I do what I want.
No!
We live in a society.
We can't just do whatever we want.
Not with dangerous beasts
like you roaming around.
- I'm not like you.
- [laughs]
Everyone says that.
[sighs] In that case...
answer this question for me.
You have two options.
"A". A society without devouring,
but with government surveillance.
"B". A society with devouring,
but zero surveillance.
Which one?
Which would you choose?
Huh?
[Legoshi] I guess, uh...
I'll go with "A".
A society with no devouring.
[Melon] You're okay with being watched?
[Legoshi]
If it keeps everybody safe, it's worth it.
- [Louis] Naru. [sighs]
- [Melon laughs]
[Louis] I told her not to go anywhere.
[Melon] This so called coexistence
and co-prosperity society is a prison
where we're all spying on each other.
Where the hell are you?
Wearing restraint like a straitjacket.
Living, but not free.
That's a prisoner.
That's what you all are.
[inhales sharply] But me...
I'm not like you.
I choose "B".
Devouring is thrilling,
delicious, pure vitality.
Gushing with so many colors of life.
You get it, right?
If you're a carnivore, that is.
[sighs]
[Legoshi]
That's what's caused me so much pain.
[Melon] Why would you
suppress your true self?
Following the rules? Being a good boy?
[Melon scoffs, laughs]
That sounds like living to you?
[Legoshi] It is, if it means
that no one has to die.
So I guess the less suffering,
the happier you are.
[inhales sharply] I see.
So it sounds like your solution is
"if it doesn't fit, wipe it out."
Ah. It's been a while
since I thought about their voices.
The good boys who tried to wipe me out
just because I existed.
- [kid 1] Jump, jump, jump!
- [kid 2] Jump!
- Do it already!
- Come on!
Why don't you be a good little herbivore?
Why don't you land
on those big sharp fangs?
Don't cats always land on their feet?
If you take after your mom,
you probably won't die.
If you don't make it, you won't
have to go to school tomorrow.
- Jump already! Do everyone a favor.
- Just jump, you coward!
- Come on, just do it!
- Jump! Jump!
- Jump!
- [kids laugh]
- [shouts]
- [scream echoes]
[Melon] I was nine,
and I killed my classmates.
But that was the first time I felt free.
But, you know...
I do wonder if I had jumped back then...
do you think I would have
grown a pair of wings?
Then I would have been
free to fly wherever I wanted.
Huh. What a perfect thought.
Anyway, keep your eye on the prize.
- [Melon chuckles]
- Huh?
No, no. No, no!
No!
[thrilling music playing]
[both grunting]
[Legoshi] You're not gonna get away.
[both groaning]
[groaning]
[Melon groans]
- Come on! Let's go!
- Huh?
[Legoshi] Move it!
- [Melon] What? Where to?
- A police station.
Listen, please don't make me carry you.
[Melon grunting]
[laughs scornfully] The police, huh?
Well, maybe jail
wouldn't be so bad for me.
But if I'm in jail, does that mean
I'll miss out on eating
that lovely rabbit?
[Legoshi] He's going to the cops,
and then I'll have Yahya
take care of my record,
so I can marry Haru.
[Melon] If I don't eat that rabbit,
I'll be filled with regret...
never knowing what delicious really means.
[Legoshi] Then we'll be together forever.
- [Melon] Just one bite would be enough.
- [Legoshi] Me and Haru.
[both stammer]
Well, now I see how strong
a carnivore can be.
- Huh?
- You've got quite a grip.
It's like iron.
Pull much harder
and you're gonna break my arm.
I'm sure as a wolf cub
that you were taught
to take it easy on those weaker than you.
Uh...
[Legoshi] He's right.
This rage running through me...
I can feel it.
[Melon grunts]
[Legoshi] Hey!
[Melon laughs maniacally]
If I had my way,
I'd gut you with my horns.
- [Legoshi grunts]
- Ooh! [laughs]
I think you've gotten quicker.
Still only slightly faster
than a sloth, though.
- [Legoshi] This isn't a joke!
- Ooh!
[Legoshi grunting]
[Melon] Whoo! [laughs]
Yeah! [laughs mischievously]
Gah!
Help me!
This wolf is going to eat me!
[panting] There he is!
- [guard 1] Who's that?
- [guard 2] Go. We got this.
Carnivores aren't allowed here.
That guy is a devourer.
He's getting away!
- [guard 1] This guy's crazy.
- [guard 2] Listen, buddy, calm down.
[groans, yells] Melon!
- [bushes rustling]
- Haru, is that you?
[gasping]
What are you doing?
I... I think I dropped my ring out here.
Why wouldn't you bring
a flashlight out here with you?
- Well, I...
- [cell phone buzzes]
[Legoshi] Hey, Louis, it's me.
You got Melon?
I lost him.
Yeah, same thing here.
-What?
- It seems like Haru ran off
- while I wasn't looking.
- What?
She might be headed your way.
- All right, got it.
- Call me back, okay?
[sighs]
Just great.
Are you... Are you looking for Haru?
Huh?
[Haru] Hmm.
So if you want to open a restaurant,
you have to think about
more than just the food, right?
Well, that's definitely something
you want to consider.
Haru! So what happened to staying put?
- Yeah, sorry about that.
- [panting]
I went to the bathroom
and this big bookshelf caught my eye.
She mentioned that she wants
to open a restaurant,
so I merely suggested
she study management as well.
- [Haru laughs]
- [Louis sighs]
Not bad advice.
Well, you found me.
Listen, even I know
when it's time to behave.
- And leaving her room is how you behave?
- I already said sorry.
- One more. It's a good one, too.
- Oh. Thank you so much.
What the... [sighs in exasperation]
Seriously!
You are unbelievable.
[Yahya] I already told you
those things don't work.
[Peach] Wait, you didn't
buy the good luck charm.
It's Legoshi. I can't find Melon anywhere.
- Haru isn't here either.
- [Haru] Is that Legoshi?
- Haru?
- [Louis] Here she is.
[sighs, stammers] Are you doing okay?
- You're not hurt, are you?
- [Legoshi] No, I... I'm okay.
I was worried.
Don't worry. It's not your fault.
I'm just glad that you're safe.
Louis' father... I have to say,
he's really an interesting guy.
He knows about so many things. [chuckles]
And he looks a bit like Louis.
[Legoshi laughs]
I'd love to meet him.
Before that,
you're the only one I wanna see.
[Haru] Oh. How about tomorrow?
All right. I'll come meet you
when you get out of school.
Nice. [giggles] See you then.
You're so great.
- [Louis] That's weird.
- Oh, um... Louis.
So what's the plan now?
Well, uh...
So I learned he's the one who's behind
all those recent devourings.
So that was Melon.
Did you go to the police?
I don't have any evidence.
Gotcha.
I really hope we catch him soon.
He's not gonna stop till we do.
Right.
I'll look into it on my end, too.
Just don't do anything crazy.
I appreciate you taking care of Haru.
Of course.
[Yahya] Hold on.
[Peach] What's this?
So you did buy one, you goofball.
Aw!
[cicadas chirping]
[Free grunting]
[grunting]
[sighs] Here you go.
All right. You guys know
how this whole thing works.
The whiskers will tell us if this year's
turf war is something we're gonna do.
If the whiskers move to the right,
then we'll pick a representative
and send them out.
But if they end up moving to the left.
[cell phone ringing]
Sorry. Hang on a sec.
- Hey, Louis!
- Oh!
Change your mind
about being our boss again?
What? Melon?
Do you know where he is?
[Free] He hasn't shown his face
around here lately.
And I know he hasn't been
around the black market.
I see.
Thanks for your help.
If you hear anything about him,
please let me know.
[sighs] You know I would if I could.
He's still the boss after all.
He's a devouring maniac
with no honor whatsoever,
but he's still your boss, huh?
I don't make the rules.
Well, I'm counting on you anyway.
MELON
[Louis] So he hasn't been
around the black market.
What do I do?
Should I go on television
and warn people about him?
[sighs] No, I can't.
Not without evidence.
It'll just cause a panic.
Should I tell Yahya what's going on?
No. He probably knows already.
- [door opens]
- Hmm?
Hey there, Louis.
Some tough opponents
will be out there today.
You don't have to speak
if you don't want to.
There's no need to risk going out
and saying the wrong thing.
Listen, just having you on the screen
for a moment is enough of a win for us.
[laughs]
[Louis sighs]
MELON
Does it smell like
cheap coffee in here to you?
Let's fix that.
We can't have our ambassador drinking
that cheap instant dishwater.
Oh, actually have you ever tried
drinking Kopi luwak?
It's really tasty.
Next time I see you, it's on me.
All right. It's showtime.
Smiles, big smiles!
[door closes]
Kopi luwak?
UDON BEBEBE
[Sunaga] Heads up. You have a delivery.
[Sheila] Okay.
It's in the First Ocean District.
You don't happen to speak
a little Ocean language?
[speaking Ocean language]
Wow! Very impressive!
I didn't graduate
from Cherryton School for nothing.
Well, that's wonderful.
I bet you could do more around here
than just filling in for Legoshi.
And speaking of Legoshi,
he didn't tell me
he was taking any time off.
Have you heard anything?
No, I haven't.
He must have a good reason
for not being here, though.
He's kind of awkward with his words.
So most of the time he gets misunderstood.
Was that how he was at school as well?
He mumbled something once.
Said the udon here is delicious
and the boss is handsome.
All right, I'm off.
You know, he really is such a good kid.
[Legoshi] Hmm.
Hmm.
Hmm. [sighs]
Louis told me about the Shishi-Gumi
technique for making decisions.
I don't know if wolf whiskers work.
Melon...
He said he quit the university.
I just need a little hint
about where he might be.
- [wind blows]
- Hmm. Hold on.
The tattoo studio?
[Melon laughs]
I think you've gotten quicker.
Still only slightly faster
than a sloth, though.
There's no way!
THE BLUE DRAGON
Can I come in?
Uh...
Hmm.
[gasps]
Uh, hey, man.
Uh... [shudders] Oh, no!
[panicked] Uh, anyone here?
[gasps]
[siren wailing in distance]
Uh... Oh, crap.
I definitely shouldn't be here.
- [siren continues]
- [panting] I'm sorry.
[tires screech]
[grunts softly]
Hey! I got eyes on a wolf!
Hold it right there!
Hey, stop!
[cop] We've got two victims on site.
Yes.
Confirming, both are deceased. Hmm.
Go ahead and send Forensics.
[closing theme song playing]